dpfks.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy contains information regarding the use and disclosure of User Data collect at MrDeepFakes.com

Our priority is the security and privacy of your Data, and MrDeepFakes.com will take all appropriate steps to mitigate he risk that this sensitive information is lost, or misused.

The use of this site is strictly limited to Users who are at least 18 years of age. All persons that do not meet this criteria are forbidden from accessing MrDeepFakes.com or viewing it's contents . We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from individuals who are not of age of majority.

DATA COLLECTED:

  * Users who are not registered may access contents of MrDeepFakes.com without any information being collected; however the visitor's IP address will be logged for security reasons.
  * Registered users are able to upload content to our site and make use of many more features. Certain personal information is requested during the time of registration, which may include: username, email address, gender and birth date. Other non-mandatory information such as relationship status, location, interests, and sexual orientation/interests are optional in the profile settings. 
  * Content uploaded to the site, along with all personal information or content contained in the video becomes public, and available for all Users to use.
  * Cookies are collected when your visit MrDeepFakes.com. Cookies may also be sent to your computer or viewing device to uniquely identify your browsing session for a better and more convenient experience.
  * Log files on our servers automatically record information that your web browser sends, such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names along with the dates and time of your request.
  * Emails are kept on our servers. If you contact us, we retain copies of that correspondence.

USES OF INFORMATION

Information and Data collected from users are used in many ways:

  * To present the Site and content to you.
  * To provide Users with information of products or services that you request from MrDeepFakes.com.
  * To notify you about changes to the Site, product or services that we offer.
  * To allow you to participate in any interactive features on the.  

  * To send promotional communications, or information about services, features, newsletters, offers, promotions or updates.
  * To monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities connected with the Site 
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

This privacy policy may be updated at anytime.
